

## NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên Tran Viet Thanh | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn



# Tran Viet Thanh

Front End Developer

Date of birth 10/07/1997

Gende

Male

Phone

0905932654

**Fmail** 

vietthanhdev@gmail.com

Address

Hai Chau, Da Nang

Website

https://www.facebook.com/viet.th anh.3767/

## **SKILLS**

Team work

MS Office

Problem solving

Communication

## **SUMMARY**

Versatile Front-End Developer with 1.5+ years of experience implementing complex web apps, particularly in SPA development utilizing React ecosystem. Developed an

education webapps, employee productivity improvement mobile app, and employment recruitment webapp using dynamic form.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **ST United Software**

9/2019 - present

Front-end developer

Main responsibilities:

- Implemented 7+ mobile-first web apps and mobile app using React, React native, Redux, and TypeScript.
- Developed more than 15+ reusable components used throughout the organization.
- Significantly improved page loading speeds for our main client's website.
- Assessed UX and UI design for technical feasibility.
- Collaborate with product team to create new features development.
- Template used: Bootstrap 4, Ant design
- Technology used: React, React Native, Redux, Typescript, ES6, Firebase, Sonarqube
- Continuous integration and delivery: CircleCI
- Version control: Github, Github Actions, BitBucket

**Sun\*** 7/2018 - 11/2018

Front-end internship

Main responsibilities:

- Convert PSD to HTML
- Implement website features development
- Delivered all appointed projects
- Template used: Bootstrap4
- Technology used: HTML, SASS, Pug, BEM
- Version control: Github

tuyendung.topcv.vn

## TIỂM NĂNG

## **EDUCATION**

## **Institute for Research & Excutive Education VN-UK**

9/2015 - 8/2019

Major: Computer Science & Engineering

GPA: 3.3

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

International English Language Testing System

Japanese Language Proficiency Test

IELTS: 5.5 overall

JLPT: N5

## **INTERESTS**

- Computer

- Music
- Traveling